

#### **PROFILE**

Motivated young professional ready to start my medical career as an Emergency Medical Technician. I plan to continue my studies in college while I work and pursue further certifications in the field, such as paramedics. I am experienced in working in a team environment, contributing to the performance of the entire organization. I have a broad set of experiences and skills in customer service which I will combine with my medical training to create positive experiences in healthcare. I am passionate about helping other people and caring for those in need.

#### CONTACT

PHONE: 281-794-8281

Address: 77 Hummingbird Breckenridge, CO 8024

EMAIL: Jpickron30@gmail.com

#### **HOBBIES**

Extreme Skiing Mountain Biking Soccer

# JACOB PICKRON

### **Emergency Medical Technician**

#### **EDUCATION**

#### **RH Health Services**

June 2019 – December 2019 Emergency Medical Technician Training San Antonio, Texas

## Alamo Community College (San Antonio) & Colorado Mountain College (Breckenridge)

September 2017 – May 2019 Basic College Courses

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### Vail Resorts | Mountain Safety

November 2017 to April 2018

- Worked in teams to set up the ski runs with safety zones and monitor areas for a dangerous activity to prevent accidents
- Reported accidents to Operations and monitored the injured <u>skier</u> until Ski Patrol arrived
- Patrolled ski areas to ensure patrons were safe and cleared ski areas ahead of severe weather and as part of shutdown operations

#### King Sooper | Store Associate

January 2018 to August 2019 - Part Time

- Greeted customers, helped locate merchandise, and assisted them with their unique needs throughout the entire visit
- Kept on top of product descriptions, store placement, and promotions to ensure positive customer experiences
- Operated the point of sale and fresh food preparation processes

#### **SKILLS**

- Emergency Medical Training
- Proficient with Microsoft Applications for report writing and spreadsheets
- Team leadership from work experiences and sports
- Diverse customer services experiences from hospitality to grocery retail <u>Jacob Pickron Resume Dec 2019.docx</u>